A Finding Aid to the Louis Bouché papers, 1880-2007, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Louis Bouché papers
1880-2007
Archives of American Art
Bouché, Louis, 1896-1969
AAA.boucloui
Archival Resource Key
5.9 Linear feet
The papers of painter and muralist Louis Bouché measure 5.9 linear feet and date from 1880 to 2007. Found within the papers are biographical material; personal correspondence, including correspondence from the extended Bouché family; writings; financial records; printed material; four scrapbooks; artwork; and photographs of Bouché, his family and friends, and his work.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
A portion of the Louis Bouché papers were loaned for microfilming and subsequently donated by the artist and his wife in 1963 and from 1972 to 1973. Additions were donated by Bouché's daughter, Jane Bouché Strong, in several accretions dating from 1978 to 1988. In 2011, Anne Strong, Jane B. Strong's executor, donated additional materials to the Archives of American Art.
Related Materials
Also found in the Archives of American Art are two oral history interviews with Louis Bouché, one conducted by John Morse, August 7, 1959, and another by William Woolfenden on March 13, 1963.
Existence and Location of Copies
The bulk of this collection was digitized in 2013 and is available on the Archives of American Art's website. Blank pages, blank versos of photographs, and duplicates have not been scanned. In most cases, only the cover, title page, and individual relevant pages have been scanned from published materials.
Conditions Governing Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center. Contact Reference Services for more information.
Biographical / Historical
Louis Bouché (1896-1969) was a painter, muralist, and educator who lived and worked in New York City.
Bouché was born in New York City to Henri and Marie Bouché. His father was an interior designer who worked with Stanford White and for Tiffany, and his grandfather, Ernest Louis Bouché, was a Barbizon school painter. After his father's death in 1909, his mother moved the family to Paris where Bouché attended art school at La Grand Chaumère. When the family moved back to America in 1915, Bouché enrolled at the Art Students League where he met fellow student and lifelong friend Alexander Brook. In 1916, Bouché was invited to become a member of Walt Kuhn's Penguin Club, and in 1918, he joined the stable of Charlie Daniel's Daniel Gallery. At this time, Bouché began exhibiting in shows organized by Julianna Force for the Whitney Studio Club, which later evolved into the Whitney Museum. In 1920, he was introduced to the Woodstock artist community and was a frequent summer resident at the colony.
Bouché met Marian Wright while they were both members of the Penguin Club, and they were married in 1921. Upon returning from their honeymoon, Bouché accepted a position managing exhibitions for Wanamaker's Belmaison Galleries, the first modern art gallery in a department store in New York. Their daughter Jane would later marry William Pène du Bois, son of Guy Pène du Bois, whom the Bouchés had known from their days in the Penguin Club. In 1926, Bouché separated from Wanamaker's and began taking commissions for mural and design work, eventually completing murals for the U.S. Department of the Interior, Radio City Music Hall, and the Pennsylvania Railroad. In addition to murals, Bouché did illustrative advertising work for various publications, including Condé Nast and Town and Country.
In 1936, Bouché joined the stable at Kraushaar Gallery, where he eventually exhibited a series of ten one-man shows. Bouché also held solo exhibitons at the Valentine Gallery, Staten Island Institute, Century Association, and Albany Institute. Beginning in 1943, Bouché taught for many years at the Art Students League and began teaching at the National Academy of Design in 1951. He received a Guggenheim Fellowship in 1936 and was the American Academy in Rome's artist in residence in 1960.
Louis Bouché died in Pittsfield, Massachusetts, on August 7, 1969.
Scope and Contents
The papers of painter and muralist Louis Bouché measure 5.9 linear feet and date from 1880 to 2007. Found within the papers are biographical material; personal correspondence, including correspondence from the extended Bouché family; writings; financial records; printed material; four scrapbooks; artwork; and photographs of Bouché, his family and friends, and his work.
Biographical material consists of family certificates and Bouché's curriculum vitae.
The bulk of the correspondence consists of letters from Bouché 's father to his mother, and of letters addressed to his daughter, Jane. These include letters Louis and Marian wrote to Jane, along with letters from her first husband, William Pène du Bois, during the early days of their courtship and marriage. The handful of letters directly addressed to Louis and Marian include correspondence from Peggy Bacon and Katherine Schmidt.
Writings include drafts of Bouché's autobiography, eight journals kept by Marian Bouché detailing their travels in the United States and abroad, four reminiscences of Bouché written by others, and a poem written by Peggy Bacon.
Personal business records consist of two ledger books, lists, and receipts documenting inventory and records of sales.
Printed material consists of clippings, exhibition announcements and catalogs, and periodicals related to Bouché's work. There are also three books from Bouché's personal library and exhibition announcements and catalogs from Walt Kuhn's Penguin Club and Wanamaker's Gallery.
Two scrapbooks include clippings, photographs, and printed material related to Bouché 's career. One scrapbook includes material related to the extended Bouché family, and one scrapbook consists of reproductions of works of art by modern French artists.
Photographic materials include ten photograph albums. Three are of Louis, Marian, and Jane, three are of Jane and her family, and four are of Louis' parents and sister's family. There are also loose prints and negatives of Bouché, his family and friends, and works of art.
Artwork consists of sketches and drawings by Louis, Jane, Henri, and Ernest Bouché. Additional sketches by Peggy Bacon, Alexander Brook, Jo Davidson, and Reginald Marsh are also included.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged as 8 series.
Missing Title
Series 1: Biographical Materials, 1880-1964 (2 folders, Box 1)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1880-2003 (1.2 linear feet; Boxes 1-2)
Series 3: Writings, 1933-1995 (.9 linear feet, Boxes 2-3)
Series 4: Personal Business Records, 1930-1974 (4 folders, Box 3)
Series 5: Printed Material, 1900-1997 (.5 linear feet; Boxes 3, 6)
Series 6: Scrapbooks, 1880-1969 (.8 linear feet; Boxes 3, 7-8)
Series 7: Photographic Materials, 1890-1994 (2.3 linear feet; Boxes 3-5, 9-10)
Series 8: Artwork, 1870-1965 (10 folders; Boxes 5, 10)
Photographs; Muralists -- New York (State) -- New York; Sketches; Scrapbooks; Travel diaries; Drawings; Painters -- New York (State) -- New York; Pène du Bois, William, 1916-1993; Bacon, Peggy, 1895-1987; Bouché, Henri L.; Bouché, Ernest; Bouché, Jane; Bouché, Marian Wright, 1895-1975; Davidson, Jo, 1883-1952; Marsh, Reginald, 1898-1954; Schmidt, Katherine, 1898-1978; Brook, Alexander, 1898-1980; Penguin Club (New York, N.Y.); Wanamaker Gallery
- Biographical Materials, 1880-1964; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 2 Folders Box 1
  Scope and Contents
  Biographical material consists of Louis Bouché's curriculum vitae and extended Bouché family marriage announcements, certificates, and death notices.
  Arrangement
  Materials are arranged by document type.
  Existence and Location of Copies
  This series has been scanned in its entirety.
  - Bouché Family Certificates and Announcements, circa 1880-1908; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Curriculum Vitae, circa 1930-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1880-2007; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 1.2 Linear feet Boxes 1-2
  The bulk of the correspondence consists of personal letters from Bouché's family, letters to Louis and Marian, and letters to Jane Bouché Strong.
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by correspondent. Undated letters are filed at the front of each folder. The series is arranged as 3 subseries.
  Missing Title
  2.1 Louis Bouché, 1920-1977
  2.2 Bouché Family, 1880-1947
  2.3 Jane Bouché Strong, 1937-2007
  - Louis Bouché, 1920-1977; 2.1; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries includes a handful of personal and professional letters addressed to Louis and Marian Bouché, including letters from artist friends Peggy Bacon, Katherine Schmidt, Louis Elshemius, and Marcel Duchamp. Love notes from Marian to Louis are also included.
    - Bacon, Peggy, 1933; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bouché, Marian, circa 1920-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Duchamp, Marcel, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Eilshemius, Louis M., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Kraushaar Galleries, 1962-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Schmidt, Katherine, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bouché Family, 1880-1947; 2.2; Archival Resource Key
    The bulk of this correspondence consists of letters from Henri to Marie Bouché. The subseries also includes letters from Henri and Marie to their children, from Louis' grandmother to the family, and from Louis and Claire to their parents.
    - Bouché, Claire to Marie Bouché (mother), circa 1883-1920; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bouché, Henri L. to Claire Bouché (daughter), 1897-1907; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Bouché, Henri L. to Louis Bouché (son), circa 1883-1908; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Bouché, Henri L. to Marie Bouché (wife), circa 1883-1908; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Bouché, Henri L. to Marie Bouché (wife), circa 1883-1908; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Bouché, Henri L. to Marie Bouché (wife), 1883-1899; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Bouché, Henri L. to Marie Bouché (wife), 1900-1905; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Bouché, Henri L. to Marie Bouché (wife), 1906-1908; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Bouché, Josephine to Claire Bouché (granddaughter), 1903-1907; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Bouché, Josephine to Marie Bouché (daughter-in-law), 1914-1918; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Bouché, Louis to Claire Bouché (sister), circa 1880-1910; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Bouché, Louis to Marie Bouché (mother), 1938-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Bouché, Marie, 1909-1916, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Bouché, Marie to Claire Bouché (daughter), circa 1905-1923; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Bouché, Marie to Henri L. Bouché (husband), circa 1883-1908; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Stone, Frederick H. DuBois, 1894-1904; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Whiton, Pete to Marie Bouché, circa 1930-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Unsigned and Illegible Names, circa 1880-1915; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Jane Bouché Strong, 1937-2007; 2.3; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries includes numerous letters from Louis and Marian; letters from Jane's first husband, William Pène du Bois, during the early days of their courtship and marriage; letters from the Bacon and Alexander families; letters from academics researching Bouché and other modern painters; and letters regarding the gift of five Belmaison glass panels to the Newark Museum.
    - A-Z, Miscellaneous, 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
      Includes letters from Ira Glackens, Jo Davidson, and Kraushaar Galleries
    - Archives of American Art, 1978-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Bacon, Belinda, 1987-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Bacon, Peggy, 1969-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Belmaison Panels, Expenses, 1984-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Belmaison Panels, Insurance, 1986-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Belmaison Panels, Taxes, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Belmaison Panels, Hirschl and Adler Galleries, 1987-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Belmaison Panels, Newark Museum, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Belmaison Panels, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Bouché, Louis and Marian, circa 1937-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Bouché, Louis and Marian, 1937-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Bouché, Louis and Marian, 1949-1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Bouché, Louis and Marian, 1952-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Bouché, Louis and Marian, 1960-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Brook, Alexander, 1971-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Brook, Alexander (Sandy), 1987-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1942 January-September; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1942 October; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1942 November; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1942 December; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1943 January-February; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1943 March; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1943 April; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1943 May-June; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1943 July; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1943 August-September; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1943 October-November; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1943 December; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1944 January; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1944 February; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1944 March-April; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1944 May; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1944 June; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1944 August-October; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Pène du Bois, William, 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Researchers, 1976-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Writings, 1933-1995; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 0.9 Linear feet Boxes 2-3
  Writings include the final draft of Bouché's autobiography, along with the original first draft and various drafts compiled and edited by Jane Bouché for possible publication. The autobiography covers Bouché's family and early life, education in France and the Art Students League, friendship with Alexander Brook, military service, the Penguin and Whitney Clubs, his courtship of Marian, their honeymoon and travels, his early art career at Washington Square South, his work for Wanamaker's, his work as a muralist, vignettes on Woodstock, artist friends, art projects, his Guggenheim fellowship, and thoughts on art and teaching.
  There are also 8 journals kept by Marian Bouché detailing her and her husband's travels in the United States and abroad from 1933 to 1963. The journal covering trips to Europe, North Stamford, and Haiti includes a handwritten draft of poems Marian and Peggy Bacon wrote for each other in response to the birth of Marian's child. Other writings include reminiscenes of Louis Bouché written by Peter Blume, Alexander Brook, Robert Coates, and Cyril Wright; and a poem to Louis Bouché by Peggy Bacon.
  Materials are arranged by author and material type. Drafts of Bouché's autobiography are ordered by chapter and include edits by Jane Bouché Strong.
  - Autobiography By Louis Bouché, Final Draft, Chapters 1-8, circa 1950-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Autobiography By Louis Bouché, Final Draft, Chapters 9-16, circa 1950-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Autobiography By Louis Bouché, Edit by Jane Bouché Strong, Chapters 1-8, circa 1980-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Autobiography By Louis Bouché, Edit by Jane Bouché Strong, Chapters 9-16, circa 1980-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Autobiography By Louis Bouché, Edit by Jane Bouché Strong, Vignettes, circa 1980-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Autobiography By Louis Bouché, Edit by Fran, circa 1980-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 1, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 2, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 3, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 4, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 5, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 6, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 7, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 8, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 9, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 10, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 11, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 12, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 13, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 14, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 15, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Chapters 16, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Vignettes #1, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Vignettes #2, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Vignettes #3, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Vignettes #4, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Vignette, Thoughts on Art, circa 1950-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Vignettes by Marian Bouché, circa 1980-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Drafts and Edits, Vignettes, Not Used, circa 1950-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Autobiography by Louis Bouché, Notes, circa 1950-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Travel Diary of Marian Bouché, Europe, North Stamford, Haiti, 1933, 1935-1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Travel Diary of Marian Bouché, Europe, Cincinnati, 1938, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Travel Diary of Marian Bouché, West Virginia, Cincinnati, Boston, 1941, 1950, 1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Travel Diary of Marian Bouché, Montreal, Des Moines, 1951-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Travel Diary of Marian Bouché, Italy, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Travel Diary of Marian Bouché, Savannah, Sarasota, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Travel Diary of Marian Bouché, S.S. Constitution, England, 1963, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Memoirs of Louis Bouché by Peter Blume, Alexander Brook, Robert Coates, and Cyril Wright, circa 1969-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Poem by Peggy Bacon, "To Saint Louis", circa 1950-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Personal Business Records, 1930-1974; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 4 Folders Box 3
  Personal business records consist of two ledger books, lists of artwork, and receipts documenting the inventory, dimension, and sales of artwork.
  - Record of Artworks, circa 1960-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Sales Ledger, Book 1, 1930-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Sales Ledger, Book 2, 1930-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Sales Receipts, 1945-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Printed Material, 1900-1997; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 0.5 Linear feet Boxes 3, 6
  Printed material consists of three coffeetable art books from Bouché's personal library; clippings, exhibition announcements, catalogs, and periodicals related to Bouché's work; and exhibition catalogs from Wanamaker's Gallery, which Bouché managed.
  The series also includes a party invitation designed by Jules Pascin and materials from Walt Kuhn's Penguin Club, including exhibition announcements, party invitations, catalogs, a poster designed by Alfred Frueh, and a Club announcement for a stag dinner in honor of Horace Brodzky.
  Materials are arranged chronologically by material type.
  This series has been partially scanned. Books, journals, and exhibition catalogs have had their covers, title pages, and relevant pages scanned.
  - Books, Exposition Universelle, Paris 1900; L'Aeronautique 1783-1922; Le Panorama, Exposition Universalle, circa 1900-1922; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Oversized material housed in Box 6, Folder 1
  - Clippings, circa 1930-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Oversized material housed in Box 6, Folder 2
  - Clippings, Other Artists, circa 1960-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, Reproductions of Artwork, circa 1940-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1938-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1970-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1990-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Exhibition Announcements, Catalogs, and Party Invitations, Penguin Club, 1917-1919; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Oversized material housed in Box 6, Folder 3
  - Exhibition Announcements, Catalogs, Wannamaker Gallery, circa 1920-1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Invitations, circa 1920; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Journals, Art, 1954-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)